{"data":[{"question":"Henry Wadsworth Longfellow was not only a poet and an author but ________ the chairman of the modern language department at Harvard university for more than eighteen years.","a":"also","b":"as well","c":"so well","d":"so","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Not only ... (but) also ...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"It's an ________ advice service.","a":"occupied (v)","b":"occupied (adj)","c":"occupation","d":"occupational","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A\/an + Noun\/noun phrase (= adj + noun).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Some important characteristics of the baroque style were a renewed interest in ornamentation and a powerful ________ of both light and shade.","a":"use","b":"useful","c":"useless","d":"to use","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A\/an +(adj) + Noun\/noun phrase( use: means the act of using something)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"I've succeeded ________ hold of the telephone number.","a":"in getting","b":"on getting","c":"upon getting","d":"about getting","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Succeed in doing sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The cabinet consists of secretaries of departments, who report to the president, give him advice, and ________ him make decisions.","a":"helping","b":"to help","c":"help","d":"with helping","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Help somebody (to) do something\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The jury isn't satisfied ________ his answer.","a":"to","b":"with","c":"about","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To be satisfied with sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Each of the intelsat satellites ________ in a fixed position from which they relay radio signals to more than seventy earth stations.","a":"remain","b":"remains","c":"remained","d":"remaining","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Unlike moderate antislavery advocates, abolitionists _____ an immediate end to slavery.","a":"demanded","b":"they demand","c":"that they demanded","d":"in that they demand","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"A few animals sometimes fool their enemies _____ to be dead.","a":"appear","b":"to appear","c":"by appearing","d":"to be appearing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be fooled by something: Be tricked by someone.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"_____ of the mourning dove is made only by the male.","a":"That the sad cooing call","b":"The sad cooing call","c":"Is the sad cooing call","d":"The cooing call is sad.","answer":"2","explain":"- We need a noun before of to form the subject\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"}]}